{"data":[{"id":0,"question":"Who pushed Bran Stark from the tower?","options":["Jaime Lannister","Jon Snow","Ned Stark","Joffrey Baratheon ","Cersei Lannister"],"correct":"Jaime Lannister"},{"id":1,"question":"What Stark's left Winterfell to travel to King's Landing?","options":["Sansa"," Ned"," Bran","Ned"," Sansa and Arya","Caitlyn"," Robb"," Arya"," Jon ","Rickon"," Ned"," Sansa"," Robb"],"correct":"Ned Sansa and Arya,"},{"id":2,"question":"Who was Deanery's married to?","options":["See Jorah","Joffrey Baratheon ","Khal Drogo","Robb Stark","Jon Snow"],"correct":"Khal Drogo"},null,{"id":4,"question":"Who became King in the North after Ned died?","options":["Jon Snow","Robb Stark","Bran Stark","Rickon Stark"],"correct":"Robb Stark"},{"id":5,"question":"Who did Jon Snow fall in love with?","options":["Cersei","The Red Witch","Gilly","Ygritte "],"correct":"Ygritte "},{"id":6,"question":"What Lannister married Sansa Stark?","options":["Cersei","Tyrion ","Tywin","Jaime"],"correct":"Tyrion "},{"id":7,"question":"Who betrayed Robb and took over Winterfell?","options":["The Lannisters","The Baratheons ","The Frays","The Boltons"],"correct":"The Boltons"},{"id":8,"question":"What season did Jon Snow die?","options":["Season 3","Season 6","Season 5","Season 4"],"correct":"Season 5"},{"id":9,"question":"Who is Jon Snow's best friend?","options":["Sam","Robb","Theon ","Tim"],"correct":"Sam"},{"id":10,"question":"What Lannister betrayed their family and became hand of the queen?","options":["Tyrion","Tywin","Cersei","Jaime"],"correct":"Tyrion"},{"id":11,"question":"Who killed Walder Fray?","options":["Sansa","Arya","Rickon","Jon "],"correct":"Arya"},{"id":12,"question":"Who won the Battle of the Bastards?","options":["Petyr Baelish","Ramsey Snow","Jon Snow","Tommon Baratheon "],"correct":"Jon Snow"},{"id":13,"question":"How did Joffrey Baratheon die?","options":["Poisoned ","Choked","Drowned","Stabbed"],"correct":"Poisoned "},{"id":14,"question":"Who was the first Stark child to die?","options":["Robb ","Sansa","Bran","Arya"],"correct":"Robb "},{"id":15,"question":"Who was the first to betrayed Rob Stark?","options":["Theon Greyjoy","Petyr Baelish","Rose Bolton","Jaime Lannister"],"correct":"Theon Greyjoy"},{"id":16,"question":"Which direwolf is still alive? ","options":["Shaggydog","Ghost","Summer","Lady"],"correct":"Ghost"},{"id":17,"question":"Who is pregnant in season 7?","options":["Daenerys Targaryen","Sansa Stark","Arya Stark","Cersei Lannister"],"correct":"Cersei Lannister"},{"id":18,"question":"Who becomes King in the North in the final episode of season 6?","options":["Rose Bolton","Bran Stark","Jon Snow","Ramsey Bolton"],"correct":"Jon Snow"},{"id":19,"question":"What two characters sleep together in the finale episode of season 7?","options":["Cersei Lannister and Jon Snow","Daenerys Targaryen and Jon Snow","Sansa Stark and Petyr Baelish","Tyrion Lannister and Daenerys Targaryen"],"correct":"Daenerys Targaryen and Jon Snow"}]}